oneartworld.com 2009-11-19

# Privacy Policy - One Art World

oneartworld.com has created this Privacy Statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for our website. 

If you have questions about oneartworld.com's privacy policy or if you feel that we are not abiding to the terms of this Privacy Statement, you should send us [feedback](http://oneartworld.com/feedbackform/). 

## Information Collection and Use

oneartworld.com collects information from users at several different points on its site and it is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. The oneartworld.com site contains links to other sites. oneartworld.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites that link to or from oneartworld.com. 

## Registration and Order Forms

In order to use some of our services, users must become a registered user (a.k.a. "Member") by first completing the registration form. This registration form requires users to supply their contact information (e.g., name and email). 

We use this customer contact information to send information to our registered users about our services. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. oneartworld.com uses cookies to save users' passwords so that they don't have to re-enter it each time they visit the site. Cookies are also used to prevent theft of site contact by e.g. automated "content scrapers". Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers) and we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

## Log Files

We use your IP (Internet Provider) address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. We use IP addresses to analyze trends and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

## Data Sharing

We do not give out, sell or rent registered user information except where needed to deliver a product or service that a registered user has ordered or to comply with valid legal process or in special cases. We may occasionally share aggregated user demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify an individual person. 

## Links to Other Websites

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that oneartworld.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of sites which link to or from oneartworld.com. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of every website they visit that collects personally identifiable information. 

## Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time oneartworld.com will request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is voluntary. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code and age). This contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used to make improvements to our website. This information may also be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis (no individual demographic information will be supplied to advertisers). 

## Security

oneartworld.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. oneartworld.com takes every precaution to protect our users' information. 

We also take precautions to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only authorized employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. 

## Correspondence With Users

We send all registered users an email confirming their password and username each time they change their username or password. We also send site and service announcement updates that contain important information about the services on our website. In addition, our Customer Support Department may, as the individual situation warrants, communicate with users via telephone or email to provide them with services they have requested or to follow-up on issues relating to their account. 

We do not sell, rent or otherwise provide our registered users email addresses to third parties. However we occasionally send postcards to our registered users informing them of our new products, services, or special auctions. Users who do not wish to receive this correspondence should send an email specifying their request along with their username, name, and address.

## Correcting/Updating Personal Information:

Registered users can update their information at any time by logging into the site (using their Username and Password) and then clicking on their user name link. 

## Note To Parents

At oneartworld.com we are aware that many children may want to visit us on the internet. Although we welcome browsing, we encourage children to receive permission from their parents before submitting any personal information over the internet. oneartworld.com believes parents should be responsible for supervising the online activities of their children and taking into account various tools that allow them to provide their children with a controlled, child-friendly internet. These tools are designed to preclude children from releasing personal information online without the permission of their parents. 

## Notification of Changes to This Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy is posted on our website. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will update our privacy policy and notify our registered users via email. 

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about oneartworld.com's Privacy Statement or the practices of this site, please send us [feedback](http://oneartworld.com/feedbackform/).
